{
    "subject": "resource/Petroglyph_Games",
    "predicate": "ontology/product",
    "object": "resource/Panzer_General:_Allied_Assault",
    "human_readable": "Petroglyph Games produced Panzer General: Allied Assault.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9191113710403442,
            "question": "Who produced the game Panzer General: Allied Assault?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7871412634849548,
            "question": "What platforms was Panzer General: Allied Assault released on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.758842945098877,
            "question": "What type of game is Panzer General: Allied Assault likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7251853346824646,
            "question": "What is the name of the game produced by Petroglyph Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7087098956108093,
            "question": "Who are some of the key factions involved in Panzer General: Allied Assault?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6664878726005554,
            "question": "Is there a sequel to Panzer General: Allied Assault?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6599387526512146,
            "question": "Can you name another game produced by Petroglyph Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.612116277217865,
            "question": "What are some common gameplay features in strategy games like Panzer General: Allied Assault?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5893008708953857,
            "question": "What is the main theme or setting of Panzer General: Allied Assault?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4631434679031372,
            "question": "What historical period does Panzer General: Allied Assault likely depict?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Petroglyph Games produced Panzer General: Allied Assault.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7183_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main theme or setting of Panzer General: Allied Assault?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7183_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common gameplay features in strategy games like Panzer General: Allied Assault?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7183_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another game produced by Petroglyph Games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7183_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7183_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents mention that \"Panzer General: Allied Assault\" was developed by Petroglyph Games."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Petroglyph Games produced Panzer General: Allied Assault. Multiple sources within the documents indicate this, such as the mention of \"Panzer General: Allied Assault is an all-new single and multiplayer digital card game... Developed by Petroglyph\" from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7183/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}